fastline.com 2017-10-19

# Fastline Privacy Policy

**Foreward**

This document outlines the complete privacy policy used by Fastline. Please print a copy of this document for your records. 

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from every page on Fastline Media Group’s websites. Any and all personal information collected on any of Fastline Media Group’s websites or by and of our brands will never be shared with an outside party, unless it is necessary to complete a transaction. 

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Fastline.com. On some pages, you can post information to the website, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include but are not limited too:  
   Name  
   Address  
   Email address  
   Phone number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you want to recommend a farmer or equipment dealer to Fastline.com, you will need to submit enough information to enable us to contact them. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:  
 Name  
 Phone Number and/or Email address

**Cookies**

Fastline.com automatically recognizes some information from the User, employing commonly-used "cookies" browser feature. Using cookies, our site will automatically recognize your member ID. A cookie is a small data file that the website writes to your hard drive. We also use cookies for a number of administrative purposes; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our site. No personal information is stored in cookies. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot read any other data off your hard drive, pass on a virus, or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not contain any information that will enable anyone to contact you by telephone, e-mail, or other means. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. Your ability to interact with Fastline.com, however, will be limited.

**Registration**

Most of Fastline.com is available without registration, but in order to take advantage of some features, you must register and create a member account. Fastline.com's online registration form requires you to provide your full name, e-mail address, postal code, acres farmed, and password for basic services. Some sections of the site may be accessible after you provide additional information about yourself.

We hope that, like many users, you will want to provide information about yourself so that we can continue to make our website more valuable to you. 

**How We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete your requested transactions. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete each transaction. With our Equipment Database, we only disclose personal information you submit to the other party after you have confirmed you want to make contact with them. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties. Contact information you supply to other dealers through Fastline.com will not be stored by Fastline.com unless you fill out the registration form during the sign-up process. By registering through Fastline.com you’ll be signed up to receive email correspondence. If you do not wish to receive email messages from us, please unsubscribe using the link provided in the email. Individual’s information is not shared with outside parties. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of users visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number visitors filled out our registration form, but we will not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We do not intend to collect individually-identifiable information from, or market our services to, children under 13 years of age. We endeavor to provide a safe online environment for users of all ages. We permit only authorized employees or suppliers, who are trained in the proper handling of customer information, to have access to customer information. Whenever we hire other organizations to provide support services, we require them to conform to our privacy standards and to allow us to audit them for compliance. We will not reveal customer information to any external organization unless we have previously informed the customer in disclosures or agreements, have been authorized by the customer, or are required by law. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Opt-Out Features**

We will remove your name from marketing or other distribution lists upon your written request. To tell us you do not want to receive communications from us, such as e-mail newsletters announcing new features, contests, or new content, or to tell us you do not want to receive communications from a third party that offers a product or service that we think would be of value to you, opt out at registration, unsubscribe using the link provided in the email, send an e-mail to [helpdesk@fastline.com](mailto:helpdesk@fastline.com) or write us at:  
   Fastline Media Group, LLC  
   PO Box 248  
   4900 Fox Run Road  
   Buckner, KY 40010.

You can decline to provide personal information to us. Please note that in some cases this will limit your interaction with the website. 

**Information Posted to Our Site**

When you post information in our equipment database listings, classified listings, on message boards or discussion groups, you grant Fastline Media Group unrestricted use of that material. Please see our Terms of Use Agreement for more information. Users should be aware that personal information voluntarily disclosed on message boards and discussion groups can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages to you from other parties.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. The personally identifiable information we collect is stored within our controlled database and we use standard, industry-wide procedures, such as firewalls and SSL (Secure Socket Layers) for credit card information. As effective as our security measures may be, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed complete security. When you register on our site, you will select a password. You will need your password to gain access to your personal information. Your password is a component of our security system. As such, it is your responsibility to protect it. Do not share your password with any third parties. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should change it immediately by going to My Account section of the website.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain from the My Account section of the website. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can update and correct factual errors in your profile or in your listings by sending us a request. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections, such as verifying your email address. 

**Policy Statement Changes**

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. 

_©2016 Fastline Media Group, LLC. All rights reserved._

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, [ helpdesk@fastline.com](mailto:helpdesk@fastline.com).
